Why? Why do you have to go?
Haru-kun, I don't want you to go!
Mii-chan, don't cry.
We'll see each other again, okay?
I hate this! Don't go, Haru-kun!
Please? Why... Why do you...
When I grow up, I'll come and get you!
So... So, when I do, let's get married!
That way we can always
be together, side by side.
Even if I die,
I'll protect you, Mii-chan!
Ow!
That way we can always be
together, side by side.
Even if I die, I'll protect you, Mii-chan!
Or do you not want to...
I do! I do!
Haru-kun, I'll marry you!
This place...
Where am I?
Seirei Gensouki
The Kingdom of Beltrum, Year 991 of the Holy Era, Early Spring
Memories of the Previous World
I'm... Rio?
You're wide open!
Not good enough!
Haruto!
Why did you hesitate in a decisive moment?!
No... Am I Amakawa Haruto?
Mii-chan...
What are these memories?
I was on the bus...
Bus? What's a "bus"?
Has the fever made me go crazy?
I...
Huh? Rio, you awake?
Wow, you're still alive?
I thought you'd be dead by now.
You really are a stubborn brat, aren't you?
Yesterday, you were reeling from a fever.
Hey! Leave that thing in
some corner of the room.
And make sure you treat it with care.
Will do!
But, man, ten gold coins
was a tasty proposition.
Ten gold coins for a simple transport job.
Though there's no way that
cargo's anything decent.
That's true.
That food looks good!
I'm hungry.
Hey, Rio!
Yes?
You stink. Go wash yourself.
You're making the food taste bad.
I'm sorry.
Amakawa Haruto lived in
a country called "Japan."
He was twenty years old
and a university student.
It seems like there was a
traffic accident, and... he died.
A traffic accident? What is that?
I don't understand!
I mean, I do, but...
Enough of that!
I am Rio!
I'm living in these filthy slums
so that I can avenge my mother!
Mom?
Why is my hair and your hair black?
Well, Rio, it's probably because your
father and I came from a far-off place.
Does everyone who lives in that
far-off place have black hair?
Yes. Your father, your grandfather,
and your grandmother all had black hair.
Really? One day I want to
meet grandma and grandpa!
Well, when you're bigger, I'll take
you there. It's a place called Yagumo.
Really? You promised, okay?
Yes, I promise.
R-Rio...
Mom...
Hey, you there.
He stinks.
It's probably best not to get too close.
It will be bad for your health.
Who are these women?
Hey, are you listening?
I'm listening. Why?
Have you seen a girl with light purple hair?
She's about the same age as you.
You'd better be honest with us.
Don't know.
Everyone, I don't think he'll
answer you if you ask that way.
Celia...
Please, leave this to me, Miss Vanessa.
I'm sorry we surprised you
like that. What is your name?
I'm called Celia.
Rio...
Rio? That's an unusual name.
My parents were immigrants.
I see. That's why your hair is black.
The thing is, Rio, I was
hoping to ask a question.
You mean about the girl with light purple hair?
I haven't seen her.
I see...
Beyond this point are the slums, right?
That's right.
Is it big?
What do you mean?
We have to go look for her, you see.
It would be better not to.
It's not somewhere a lady dressed in
clothes as nice as yours should go.
Nice clothes?
What kind of clothing do the
women who live in the slums wear?
What kind?
The same as common people,
only completely tattered.
I see.
Celia...
If that's the case, we should
change our clothes and come back.
What are you saying? If we
don't hurry, that girl will...
That's right!
But we aren't moving as
part of an official action.
If we make a wrong move and
cause a disturbance...
I'm sure that's not something
you want, Lady Christina.
Th-Then let's hurry back and find clothing.
Celia!
Just to make sure, can you look for
a magic response in the vicinity?
Just a moment, please.
Area...
Huh?
Search!
What is this?
Oh, my. You're...
Has something happened to that child?
It appears that he's overflowing with
quite a large quantity of magic power.
He has the potential necessary to use magic.
Ah, yes. There are some like
that even among the orphans.
He has magic power?
Magic? This strange light is magic?
And are there any other reactions?
There aren't.
The only magic reactions the search
caught were ours and that boy's.
I see.
She must be in there after all.
We have no conclusive evidence, but...
Can it be...
for now, all we can do is ready a
change of clothing and go ourselves.
that those people can't see this light?
It seems that way.
Oh! Here.
Payment for the information.
Please accept it.
Well, then, goodbye.
Thank you!
Greater silver coins?!
There are so many!
I've return—
Dang it.
Wh-Who is this guy?
Haruto!
We don't have time right now.
I will teach you about od, and how
to use your magic power.
Learn it by remembering this feeling.
H-How to use magic?
Sharpen your senses.
There is light coming from
your body, isn't there?
Use that light to increase your physical
abilities and make your body stronger.
Take that image and...
Enchant Physical Ability!
You rotten kid...
Who are you?
Don't act cocky with me!
Wh-What's that?
I knew it.
I'll untie you right now. Just wait a minute.
P-Please, save me!
Won't you please... take me to the castle?
The castle?
I beg of you. If you speak to
my father... he will reward you.
Your father?
H-Hey!
This girl... She's the girl Celia and
the others were looking for, isn't she?
You there! Stop!
Lady Christina! Please, wait!
You lied to us, didn't you?!
Flora! Flora!
Vanessa! See to Flora!
Yes, milady!
What were you plotting,
kidnapping my younger sister?
What?
I-It's not like that! She asked me to—
You're saying she asked you to?!
Please, calm down, Lady Christina.
I am calm. But she's...
Celia, Roanna, look after Lady Flora.
She is unconscious, but it
appears she is unharmed.
Yes, Miss!
Understood.
Will you tell us what happened, in detail?
Like I said. That girl asked me to—
You're lying! That girl would
never ask to be kidnapped!
Please, listen until the very end.
Th-That hurts!
L-Let go, you loathsome thing!
Let go of her hands.
And Lady Christina,
please stop provoking him.
It's his fault! I'll have him
charged with lèse-majesté!
This boy doesn't know that
you are from the royal family.
We must hear from him what happened.
Then hurry and restrain him!
That is the state of things, young man.
You will accompany us to the castle.
I don't want to.
I'm sorry, but this isn't
a request. It's an order.
All I did was rescue her.
Just ask her when she wakes.
It's no good. We'll have you
tell us what you know yourself.
It seems like trying to protest
here would only be a waste of time.
Just to talk, then.
Yes. If you are innocent,
they should release you.
Sir Alfred! We've found
a man still breathing.
Restrain him and bring him out!
He could be an accomplice to the kidnapping.
Understood, sir.
Don't push! Stand back!
My, my...
I suppose I have no choice.
H-Hey! What's wrong?
What's going on?
H-He's dead.
What?
What is all of this?!
I thought we were just supposed to talk!
I am the Vice Captain of the Knights
of the Royal Guard, Charles Arbor.
You will tell me all you know of
the kidnapping of the second princess.
You can't be serious!
I would rather not have to get rough here.
If you'll agree to cooperate with our inquiry,
I wouldn't mind immediately
releasing you from this situation.
First, admit to your complicity in
the kidnapping of the second princess.
I didn't do anything like that!
You assisted in the kidnapping of
Princess Flora. Isn't that right?
I haven't... done anything.
What a fool.
Princess Flora!
Vanessa...
Where am I?
Your bedroom, Princess Flora.
Please, have some.
Thank you.
May I ask you to explain what's happened?
Your Highness, the thing is...
Investigation? Why?
There is a need to determine if the content
of the boy's testimony is true or not.
In that case, please summon him here.
That would... That would be very difficult.
Why?
That boy is no more than a simple orphan.
I believe it would require the
consent of His Majesty, the King.
Then please hurry and make
the necessary arrangements.
I cannot allow him to meet
with any inconvenience!
Understood, Your Highness.
I will go as well.
Celia...
I'm counting on you.
As you will.
Your Highness.
You rotten brat! Hurry up and cough
up what you know about the kidnappers!
I-I have... nothing more... to say.
You little—
Vice Captain! If you go too far, he'll die!
Silence!
We of the Knights of the Royal Guard
were charged with her escort,
and we allowed Princess Flora to be abducted!
If we don't restore our reputation,
things won't end well for you, either!
Still...
What is going on here?!
With the authority granted me as
Vice Captain of the Knights of the Royal Guard,
I am conducting a lawful interview.
I believe my men relayed that
the investigation of that boy
was to be handled courteously.
Indeed, they did say that.
None of that matters now!
Hurry up and let him down!
No.
It is highly likely that the brat was
involved in the kidnapping of Princess Flora.
That very same Princess Flora says
that she owes that young man her life.
Wh-What?
Her Highness has awakened?
I-I see. Well, that's the
most important thing.
You! Let him down!
Sir!
Are you all right?
Don't touch me...
I-I'm so sorry! I'll heal you right away!
Let's go!
I-I'm so glad!
Are you all right? Does anything hurt?
Oh! I'm sorry! You must be surprised.
Where am I?
In the royal palace.
H-How...
I'm so sorry. We made you go
through something terrible.
Was it you who healed me?
Yes.
I'm learning magic at the
Beltrum Royal Academy, too.
I'm Celia.
Celia Claire. Do you remember me?
Area...
Payment for the information.
Please accept it.
Thank you!
From back then...
Thank you very much.
Not at all! We're the ones who
should be apologizing to you.
I'm so sorry you had to go through
all of that because of us.
It's not like you did anything wrong.
More importantly, what's going
to happen to me now?
It seems you are to be granted an
audience with His Majesty, the King.
He says he wants to express his
gratitude to you in person.
An audience?
Then, I apologize for the imposition,
but could you teach me the
manners needed for an audience?
I can't go see the king
without knowing any protocol.
Of course! It's no trouble at all!
I look forward to working with you, Rio.
Now, the young man who rescued
Her Highness, Princess Flora, will enter!
Next Time
Royal Academy
"Royal Academy."
Spirit Chronicles
Exciting Bonus Manga
I had
a dream
that
I used
magic...
...to turn
anyone
who picked
on Rio
into a
cat.
By Minazuki Futago
Even you
don't have
that kind
of magic,
right?
can't
be...